Hello.
こんにちは
Sorry.
すいません
It's cute.
可愛いね
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
Can I do something like a light interview?
ちょっと軽いインタビューみたいなのをしていい?
yes.
はい
Do you want to be in gravure?
グラビアになりたいんだっけ?
I want to be in gravure.
グラビアになりたくて
Do you want to be a gravure?
グラビアになりたい?
Do you want to become a gravure idol?
グラビアアイドルになりたい?
Yes, I want to be.
はい、なりたいです
Why do you want to be?
なんでなりたいの?
There is someone named Ai Shinozaki, and I admire you.
あ なたの方がいて、 それが 篠崎愛さんという方で 憧れて
I also started thinking that I wanted to become a gravure idol.
私 も グラビアアイドルになりたいなって思って きました
I like Ai Shinozaki.
篠崎愛ちゃん好きなんだ
What do you like about it?
どんなところが好きなの?
She was so cute and had a wonderful smile, ever since I was little.
なんか可愛くて 笑顔も素敵で 私の小さい頃から
do your best.
頑 張って
If I work hard, I can sleep.
頑張ったら寝れるから
I will do my best.
頑張ります
How old are you now?
今、いくつだっけ?
I'm 18 years old now.
今は18歳です
Did you go to school?
学校出たんだっけ?
that's right.
そうです
Graduated from high school.
高校卒業して
You just graduated.
卒業したばっかだじゃん
Where are you from?
出身は?
This is Kagoshima.
鹿児島です
Well, I've been in a situation all the way.
じゃあ、はるばる状況してきたんだ
that's right.
そうです
Due to my current situation, I feel like I'm living alone.
状況して、一人暮らして って感じです
Are you living alone now?
今、一人暮らしか、じゃあ
Are you used to it?
慣れた?
Well, I haven't done any housework at all yet.
いやー、まだ 全然、家事とかが いなくて
It's difficult, isn't it?
難しいよね
So, are you going to start working part-time now?
じゃあ、バイトも もう始めるの?
I agree.
そうですね
I'm also thinking of starting a part-time job.
アルバイトも 始めようと思って
What do you want?
何したいの?
I'm interested in theme parks.
テーマパークとか興味あるよ
I like things like entertaining.
楽しませることとか 好きなんで
It's true that my idols do this a lot too.
確かに、うちのアイドルも 結構やったりしてるね
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
I'll introduce you.
紹介してあげる
Is it true?
本当ですか?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
That's scary.
怖いね
No, not at all.
いやいや、全然
Did you do any club activities?
部活とかやってたの?
I was doing it.
やってました
How many parts was it?
何部だったの?
I am the manager of the brass band.
吹奏楽部の マネージャーです
Manager of the brass band?
吹奏楽部の マネージャー?
I'm not a musical instrument leader myself?
自分は楽器リーダーしない?
I agree.
そうですね
I like being supported.
支える方が好きなんで
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏いる?
I'm here.
います
Oh, are you there?
あ、いるんだ?
Locally?
地元に?
that's right.
そうです
I started a long-distance relationship with Kutsujima.
株島の方に 遠距離恋愛になっちゃったんです
I agree.
そうだね
Well, I don't think it's good to have a boyfriend, so I thought about it for a while.
あ ん まり、彼氏いるのは 良くないと思うから ちょっと考え
I don't think so.
ない とね
that's right.
そうです
What should I do?
どうする?
What if I have to break up with you for work?
仕事のために 別れなきゃってなったら
But become a club or an idol
でも、クラブやアイドル になる
I might think about it since it's number one after all.
や っぱり一番にあるので 考えるかもです
Shall I think about it?
考えちゃうか
I'll give you some support.
ちょっと応援するよ
Really.
本当に
You can do it if you try hard.
頑張ればなれるからさ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Well, I'm going to take some pictures today.
ちょっとまあ、今日色々撮影ね
Well, everyone is doing it, but if you do it,
ましたりして まあ、みんなやってるんだけど やったら、
I want to film it on TV.
テレビで撮りたいとかする
Can I film it on TV?
テレビで撮れるんですか?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Do you want to go out?
出たい?
I want to go out.
出たいです
I want my parents to support me, so I want to perform a famous TV song.
親とかにも 応援してもらいたいので 有名なテレビ曲 出たい
is.
です
Totally.
全 然全然
Are you popular?
モテるっしょ?
No, I'm not popular at all.
いやいや、全然モテないです
Really?
本当に?
It's important to be popular.
モテるのは大事なことなんで
I agree.
そうですね
So, by the way, what should I do?
じゃあ、ちなみに どうしようか
3 sizes 3 sizes?
3サイズを 3サイズですか
It's important.
大事だ
Kana 15 is about 58, which is about 15.
かな 15 って 58ぐらいで 15ぐらいです
It's okay, it's okay.
いいじゃん、いいじゃん
It looks like a real thing.
本級っぽなね
No, not at all.
いやいや、全然
What about your chest?
胸は?
My breasts are A cup.
胸は Aカップです
It's pretty big.
結構大きいのね
I don't know yet.
今はまだわかんない
yes.
はい
Because style is the most important thing.
スタイルが一番大事だからさ
I agree.
そうですね
That's quite a lot.
結構あれだね
Do you feel similar to Ai-chan?
アイちゃんと似てる 感じなのか
That's what I'm aiming for, so what's your experience?
目指してるんで 体験は
Well, I'd like to take some photos with some poses.
じゃあちょっとポーズとか 撮りたいんだけど
Let's take a moment, shall we?
ちょっと じゃあ 撮ってみるか
is that so.
そうですか
Isn't it a swimsuit or something?
水着とかじゃないんですか
Swimsuit, I don't have it today, I always wear swimsuit, but what now?
水着ね、ちょっと今日はなくて いつも水着なんだけど 今は何?
underwear?
下着?
It's underwear.
下着です
Well, it's the same thing.
まぁ同じようなもんだから
Is it okay to wear underwear?
下着でいいんですか?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
We have to do something like a swimsuit examination.
水着審査みたいな しなきゃいけないから
A little boobs.
ちょっとおっぱい
Spread your breasts.
おっぱい広げて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Spread it out.
広げてくれ
It's in good shape.
いい形してるわ
good?
いい?
I think it's good.
いいと思うよ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Then hold me close to your chest
じゃあ胸寄せて
Your body is beautiful.
体 きれいだね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Weight?
重さ?
Look at this, can you see the weight?
ちょっと重さを ちょっとこれ見て 分かる?
How many grams?
何グラムか
I don't understand.
分かんないですね
I'll also check the weight.
重さも調べるんですね
weight and softness
重さと柔らかさって
Just check.
確 認するだけ
Because I'm seriously doing this.
これマジやってるから
To everyone?
みんなにですか?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
I liked the softness.
柔らかさよかった
It's soft.
柔らかいね
picture?
え?
Seriously?
マジ?
Is this necessary?
これ必要だから?
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
By the way
ちなみに
How about something like a successful person?
成 功員みたいなのって どう?
Did you do it recently?
最近した?
I haven't done that recently.
最近はしてないです
When will it be the last time?
最後にしたらいつくらい?
Before coming here.
こっち来る前だ
yes.
はい
Was it him?
彼でした?
that's right.
そうです
That's fine, I have to do it.
結構ね、しないといけないんで
Is it good for photography?
撮影にいいですか?
Jajaja.
じゃじゃじゃ
Gravure etc.
グラビアとか
Hormones and things like that.
ホルモンとかそういう
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
Is it necessary?
必要ですか?
I'm confirming this.
これ確認だから
This is going to get messy.
これボロリしたりするんだよ
When wearing a swimsuit.
水着の時
often.
よく
That means it's necessary.
必要なってことですね
I have to look at the swimsuit size.
それ水着のサイズとか見なきゃいけないから
Actually, there are women like this.
本当はこういうの女らしがいるんだけど
If I don't see how big it is, I'll fall apart.
どんくらいこれ大きいか見ないとボロリしちゃうし
It's both.
2つとものです
That's right.
そうだよ
This is pretty easy to mess up.
これ結構ボロリしやすいね
It's easy.
しやすいね
Like a swimsuit.
水着みたいに
Will it happen?
なっちゃうか
good
いい
Yo.
よ
You have a popular body type.
人 気の体型してるね
is that so.
そうですか
nice.
いいね
Please send it again.
もう一回寄せて
In the front mirror.
前鏡に
I'll be refreshed tomorrow.
明日ペリッとしてるから
You're a beautiful person.
きれいな人してんじゃん
Like the rag from earlier.
さっきのボロリみたいな
I want you to stop doing it so much.
あんまりやめてほしい
Also check?
確認も?
I just finished drinking.
さっき飲んで済んだの
But that's how it is.
でもそういうのさ
Sleep.
寝て
Is that so?
そうなんですか
It's not like I want to sell it.
なんかさ、売れたいわけじゃん
yes.
はい
In order to sell.
売れたいのためには
Then I won't do it.
じゃあやんないから
Because I asked you to come today.
今日来てもらったから
I'll give you my money too.
俺のお金もあげるし
Thank you for coming.
せっかく来てもらって
Because we have to do that kind of review.
そういう審査をしなきゃいけないから
Just look at the naked body.
ちょっと 裸だけ見る
Just ask me to take my swimsuit.
水着だけ取ってもらって
Is it possible to have only the whole body removed?
全身だけ取り取らせてもらうことってできる?
Is it takan?
たかんですか?
That's all I want you to do.
それだけやってほしい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Well, it's over now.
じゃあもう終わるから
No, no.
違う違う
I'll just take the naked body now.
もう裸だけ取る
Because I don't touch it.
触らないから
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
Then do it yourself.
じゃあ自分で
I don't do my own breasts.
自分でおっぱいやんないね
picture?
え?
No, no.
違う違う
It won't end if you don't take it.
取んないと終わんないよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Don't you have anything scary to do?
別に怖いことしないか?
It's scary.
怖いです
Don't do anything scary?
怖いことしない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Come and see.
来てごらん
I only take the naked body.
裸だけ取るんだけど
It's scary.
怖いです
Aren't you scared?
怖くない?
I want to go home.
帰りたいです
It's not scary.
怖くないよ
No, no.
違う違う
You're saying just remove the nose and face.
鼻顔取るだけって言ってんじゃん
I want to quit.
もうやめたいです
why?
なんで?
Please cry.
泣いてください
You want to cry, right?
泣いたいんでしょ、だって
Become an idol.
アイドルに
I want to cry though.
泣いたいけど
It's just a little bit, so come on.
ちょっとだから、来てほら
Good, good, good.
いいよいいよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Boobs, then.
おっぱい、じゃあ
With a brush.
ブラシで
I don't like it.
嫌です
why?
なんで?
Please stop.
やめてください
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
Wait a minute, come over here.
ちょっとじゃあ、 こっち行って
Just come here.
こっちだけ来て
Let's sit down here.
座ろう、こっち
I won't sit down, I won't sit down.
座らない、座らないから
Let's sit here.
こっち座ろう
It's okay, sit down.
大丈夫、座って
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
I won't do anything painful.
痛いことはしない
Really.
本当に
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Well then, I won't do anything painful or unpleasant.
じゃあ、痛いことか、そういうのは嫌なことはしないよ
Really.
本当に
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
Hey, do your hair.
ちょっと、髪してくれ
Just look.
見るだけだ
why?
なんで?
I'll give you all the money.
全くお金あげるから
I said this is good for removing hair from your nose.
これ、鼻から毛取るのがいいって言ったじゃん、
some time ago.
さっき
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
I really want to stop it.
やっぱり、止めたい
It's okay, don't be scared.
大丈夫、怖くないよ
You want to be, right?
なりたいでしょ、だって
I don't like it, I want to quit.
嫌、やめたいです
I hate it, I hate it, I hate it.
嫌、嫌、嫌、嫌
Why do you want to quit?
なんでやめたいの?
Was it wrong?
違った?
But, look, I took the trouble to prepare.
でも、ほら、せっかく準備してさ、
Do it like this.
こうやってやってさ
If you want to quit, you'll be in trouble.
や めたいじゃ困るでしょ
That's how you do that kind of work.
そんな仕事、そうやってやるの
Well then, from now on.
じゃあ、これから
You won't do it.
やんないでしょ
Get ready!
すげー準備してさ
I'm doing it.
やってんだよ
It's okay, but you can stop it.
別にいいけど、やめても
I don't mind if I give up, but I have to pay for the hotel, etc.
やめてもいいけど、 ホテル代とか、
You'll have to pay for everything, everything.
いろいろ、 全部ね、かかってるのを 払ってもらうことになる
Yo.
よ
So I have no choice but to finish it for now.
だから、 とりあえず終わらせるしかないから
Well then, I have to bring this material as well.
じゃあ、俺もこれ、 素材持ってかないといけないから
That's fine, isn't it?
それ、いいでしょ、それ
Well then, I need to see some nakedness.
じゃあ、ちょっと裸ぐらい見ないと
Because it's no good.
ダメだから
Can you pay?
払える?
Because.
だって
That's impossible, right?
無理でしょ
Quite a few hundred thousand.
結構もう、何十万か
I'm going to send this to my parents' house.
これ、じゃあ実家に 送ることになるよ
Please stop.
やめてください
Right?
でしょ
You don't like your parents' home, do you?
実家は、嫌でしょ、そんな
Kagoshima, hey, I know your address, but...
鹿児島、 ねえ、住所と知ってるけど、
That's no good, right?
ダメでしょ
You don't like it, do you?
嫌でしょ
So, hey, hey.
だから、ちょっと、ほら
I want to touch it.
触ったいぞ
I want to touch your skin, or rather, your face.
触ったいっていうか、肌顔を そう、
Just look.
見るだけだから
You can't pay.
払えないでしょ
Okay, just look.
いいでしょ、見るだけ
I'll watch this from now on.
これ見るから、今から
Can you pay for this?
これ払える?
You can't pay.
払えないでしょ
Hey, boobs.
ちょっと、おっぱい
The skin has to be removed.
肌、取らなきゃいけないから
Just take it.
取るだけです
copper?
どう?
Just take it.
取るだけ
It's okay, aren't you scared?
大丈夫、怖くない?
Aren't you scared?
怖 くない?
Please stop.
やめてください
That's fine.
いいです
Please stop.
やめてください
It's okay, it'll be over soon.
大丈夫、すぐ終わるから
It's okay, right?
大丈夫でしょ
This is this.
こんなって、これ
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
Hmm, scary.
うーん、怖い
picture?
え?
It's not scary.
怖くないよ
After lying down.
横になってから
Just lie down and take it.
横になって、取るだけだから
Really, just take it.
本当、取るだけです
That's right, see.
そうだよ、ほら
It's okay, aren't you scared?
大丈夫、怖くない?
Look, straight.
ほら、まっすぐ
No, after lying down.
違う、横になってから
Look, this way.
ほ ら、こっち
Would you like me to face you?
こっち向いてもらう?
This way?
こっち?
Stretch your legs.
足伸ばして
This way.
こっち
Lie down.
横になって
Look, to the boobs.
ほら、おっぱいに
Can't you see?
見えない?
I can't see it.
見えないです
It's okay, don't touch it.
大丈夫、触れない
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
Show me this.
見せて、これ
Is it okay?
いいの?
This won't end.
これじゃ終わらないよ
You want it to end, right?
終わりたいでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
stop?
やめる?
Or maybe.
それとも
I'm going to my parents' house, is it okay?
実家に行くけど、大丈夫?
Do it.
やって
Oh no, look.
やだって、ほら
I have to see the boobs for now.
おっぱい、とりあえず見ないといけない
Hey.
ねえ
Yeah.
うん
Hands, here.
手、こっち
Lie down.
横になって
Look.
ほら
Look, you have to see it all.
ほら、見ないといけないじゃん、全部
It's like, I can't stop.
やめられないじゃんだって、そんな
Is it okay to just take it?
取るだけって、いいの?
Just take it, just take it.
取るだけ、取るだけだよ
Here too.
ここも
ここ も
No need, no need.
必要ないです、必要ない
必要ない、必要ない
Look, you often play MG, right?
ほら、よくMGとかやるでしょ?
Try it.
やってごらん
What is MG?
MGって
Because I have to.
やんなきゃいけないから
Yeah.
うん
Don't do it, don't do it.
やるな、やるな
Is it okay?
いいの?
I have to do it.
やんなきゃ
I won't watch it.
見ないよ
Hey, MG.
ほ ら、MG
Please take it with your hand.
手で受けてくれ
Show me.
見せてくれ
Look.
ほ ら
Wait, open up more.
ちょっと、もっと開く
No, because there is something like this.
いや、こういうのあるから
You know, right?
知ってるでしょ?
This is what it says
こう いうのが
It's necessary.
必 要だよ
Wait a minute, you'll see it and it'll be over.
ちょっとじゃあ、見たら終わりね
That's it, right?
それだけでしょ
If you've come this far, you have no choice but to show it.
ここまで来たら見せるしかないでしょ
Are you done?
終わりますか?
So.
それで
End, end.
終わる終わる
I have to see it.
見なきゃ
Because it won't end.
終わんないから
It ends.
終わります
It'll end.
終わるよ
If you look.
見たら
I don't see it.
見ない
I don't like it.
嫌です
Well, it won't end if you don't watch it.
じゃあ、見ないと終わんないから
Sister, show me.
姉ちゃん、見せて
Everyone is doing this.
こういうのみんなやってんだよ
Everyone is doing it.
みんなやってんの
That's right.
そうなんです
Because I want it to stop.
だってもうやめてほしい
Stop it, stop it.
もう やめるやめる
Well then, okay.
じゃあ、いいよ
Have your legs open.
足開いてもらう
Now, let me open your legs.
じゃあ、足開いてもらう
This is because Gemi will appear.
これね、ゲミって現れるから
If you don't see this, it's no good.
これ見ないと、 ダメなの
I said it.
言ったじゃん
I have to fly naked.
裸は飛んないと
It's going to end.
終わっちゃうよって
It won't end
終わんないよ
That's it.
って
Let me see.
見 せてごらん
So what do we do now?
じゃあ、もうどうする?
I'm contacting my family.
実家に連絡してるよ
You don't like it, right?
嫌でしょ?
Now, just use your hands.
じゃあ、手だけでごらん
Just use your hands.
手だけでごらん
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
Choose.
選んで
Which one?
どっち?
Because it won't hurt.
痛いことしないから
It's okay.
大丈夫 で
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Please cut corners.
手抜けてごらん
I'll give you money.
お金をあげるから
It's got a lot of hair.
すごい毛入ってるじゃん
You don't have to rub it.
擦らなくてもね
Look.
ほら
Cut corners.
手抜けて
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わるから
Spread your legs properly.
足開いて、ちゃんと
MG opens its feet.
MG開脚
Open it.
開 いて
a little bit.
ちょっと
what?
何?
I have to see something.
何かも見ないと
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わる
すぐ終わるから
So, can you pay?
じゃあ、お金払える?
You won't pay.
払わないでしょ
don't pay
払 わないで
Sho.
しょ
I have to see it.
見 ないと
It won't end, will it?
終わんないでしょ
I have to see it.
見ないと
Move away.
どけてよ
どけてごらん
why?
なんで?
Won't you show me?
見せてくれない?
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わる
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Here too.
ここも
Because it won't end.
終わんないから
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
Please end this.
これで終わりにしてくれ
do.
する
Are you okay.
大丈夫
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って